<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Maxwell Sport</string>

    <string name="login_username">Username</string>
    <string name="login_password">Password</string>
    <string name="login_button">Log In</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <!-- Nagłowki widoków -->
    <string name="toolbar_about_title">About</string>
    <string name="toolbar_exercise_details_title">Exercise Details</string>
    <string name="toolbar_exercise_title">Exercises</string>
    <string name="toolbar_exercise_group_title">Atlas</string>
    <string name="toolbar_cardio_title">Cardio</string>
    <string name="toolbar_cardio_summary_title">Run Summary</string>
    <string name="toolbar_profile_title">Profile</string>
    <string name="toolbar_settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="toolbar_settings_language_title">Language</string>
    <string name="toolbar_settings_tab_title">Default Tab</string>
    <string name="toolbar_settings_theme_title">Theme</string>
    <string name="toolbar_training_day_title">Training Day</string>
    <string name="toolbar_training_title">Training</string>
    <string name="toolbar_training_summary_title">Training Summary</string>

    <!-- Domyslne warości pól -->
    <string name="default_timer_value">00:00</string>
    <string name="default_distance_value">0.00</string>
    <string name="default_zero_value">0</string>

    <!-- Nazwy pól w navigation drawer -->
    <string name="nav_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="nav_training">Training</string>
    <string name="nav_cardio">Cardio</string>
    <string name="nav_atlas">Atlas</string>
    <string name="nav_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="nav_logout">Log Out</string>
    <string name="nav_about">About</string>

    <!-- Profile Fragment -->
    <string name="profile_user_name">User name</string>
    <string name="profile_user_email">email@example.com</string>
    <string name="profile_active_since">Active since: 00.00.0000</string>
    <string name="profile_statistics">Statistics:</string>
    <string name="profile_training_form">Training form:</string>
    <string name="profile_running_form">Running form:</string>

    <!-- pola do tablicy ze statystykami treningu -->
    <string name="profile_last_training_date">Last training date:</string>
    <string name="profile_last_training_date_value">-</string>
    <string name="profile_last_training_duration">Last training duration:</string>
    <string name="profile_average_training_duration">Average training duration:</string>
    <string name="profile_longest_training_duration">Longest training duration:</string>
    <string name="profile_last_exercise_amount">Last exercise amount:</string>
    <string name="profile_average_exercise_amount">Average exercise amount:</string>
    <string name="profile_biggest_exercise_amount">Biggest exercise amount:</string>

    <!-- pola do tablicy ze statystykami biegów -->
    <string name="profile_last_run_date">Last run date:</string>
    <string name="profile_last_run_date_value">-</string>
    <string name="profile_last_run_duration">Last run duration:</string>
    <string name="profile_average_run_duration">Average run duration:</string>
    <string name="profile_longest_run_duration">Longest run duration:</string>
    <string name="profile_last_run_distance">Last run distance:</string>
    <string name="profile_average_run_distance">Average run distance:</string>
    <string name="profile_longest_run_distance">Longest run distance:</string>
    <string name="profile_last_run_pace">Last run pace:</string>
    <string name="profile_average_run_pace">Average run pace:</string>
    <string name="profile_biggest_run_pace">Best run pace:</string>

    <!-- Training Fragment-->
    <string name="training_title">Training 1</string>
    <string name="training_information_label">Details</string>
    <string name="training_exercise_group">Muscle groups:</string>
    <string name="training_exercise_group_value">-\n-\n-</string>
    <string name="training_exercise_amount">Exercise amount:</string>
    <string name="training_weight">Weight:</string>
    <string name="training_sets">Sets:</string>
    <string name="training_reps">Reps:</string>
    <string name="training_completed">COMPLETED</string>
    <string name="training_not_completed">NOT COMPLETED</string>
    <string name="training_popup_description">Description</string>
    <string name="training_timer">Time [min]</string>

    <!-- Training Summary Fragment-->
    <string name="training_summary_title">Training summary</string>
    <string name="training_summary_time">Time spent training:</string>
    <string name="training_summary_exercise_amount">Completed exercises:</string>
    <string name="training_summary_rate_title">Rate your performance</string>

    <!-- Cardio Fragment -->
    <string name="cardio_timer">"Time [min]"</string>
    <string name="cardio_distance">"Distance [km]"</string>
    <string name="cardio_pace">"Pace [min/km]"</string>

    <!-- Cardio Summary Fragment-->
    <string name="cardio_summary_title">Run summary</string>
    <string name="cardio_summary_time">Time spent running:</string>
    <string name="cardio_summary_distance">Distance traveled:</string>
    <string name="cardio_summary_pace">Average pace:</string>
    <string name="cardio_summary_rate">Rate your performance</string>

    <!-- Atlast Fragment -->
    <string name="atlas_exercise_group_name">Exercise group name</string>
    <string name="atlas_exercise_name">Exercise name</string>
    <string name="atlas_exercise_description">Description:</string>
    <string name="atlas_exercise_description_content">Bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla bla</string>
    <string name="atlas_exercise_difficulty">Difficulty:</string>
    <string name="atlas_exercise_difficulty_name">Medium</string>

    <!-- Ćwiczenia -->
    <string name="exercise_group_1_name">Biceps</string>
    <string name="exercise_group_2_name">Triceps</string>
    <string name="exercise_group_3_name">Shoulders</string>
    <string name="exercise_group_4_name">Chest</string>
    <string name="exercise_group_5_name">Back</string>
    <string name="exercise_group_6_name">Legs</string>
    <string name="exercise_group_7_name">Abs</string>

    <string name="exc_biceps_1_name">Alternation bending elbows with dumbbells with rotation of wrist and elbows elevation</string>
    <string name="exc_biceps_2_name">Alternation bending elbows with dumbbells (elbow propped on thigh)</string>
    <string name="exc_biceps_3_name">Alternation bending elbows with dumbbells hold neutrally</string>
    <string name="exc_biceps_4_name">Alternate flexing forearms using cable row</string>
    <string name="exc_biceps_5_name">Reverse grip lat pull down</string>
    <string name="exc_biceps_6_name">Bending elbows with barbell held with wide-grip</string>

    <string name="exc_biceps_1_description">In sitting position, dumbbells is held with wide-grip, forearms in average setting:\n- take breath and bend forearm, making the half-turn of the wrist on the outside before forearm finds itself in horizontal position;\n- complete movement with lifting elbows and exhale.\nThis exercise involves brachioradialis, brachialis muscle, biceps, front part of deltoid.</string>
    <string name="exc_biceps_2_description">In sitting position, elbow propped on inside part of thigh:\n- take breath and bend forearm;\n- exhale in the final phase of movement.\nThis isolated exercise allows to control range, speed and accuracy of movement. It involves mainly biceps and brachialis muscle.</string>
    <string name="exc_biceps_3_description">In standing or sitting position, dumbbells are held by both hands with wide-grip, forearm in middle position:\n- take breath and bend both forearms simultaneously or alternately;\n- exhale in final phase of movement.\nThis exercise develops best brachioradialis. It affects also on biceps and brachialis muscle.</string>
    <string name="exc_biceps_4_description">In standing position, face forward, cable row hand is held with wide-grip:\n- take breath and bend forearm;\n- exhale in final phase of movement.\nThis exercise allows to concentrate effort within biceps and promotes intense muscle blood supply.</string>
    <string name="exc_biceps_5_description">In standing position, standing centrally to lift, arm outstretched, lift hands are held with reverse grip:\n- take breath and bend forearms;\n- exhale in final phase of movement.\nThis exercise which often ends workout arms muscles allows to develop biceps, mainly its pre-streached short head and biased in position of spread shoulders; it also develops brachialis.\nThis exercise cannot be perform with heavy load. It\'s important to focus on the feeling of contraction of internal part of biceps.</string>
    <string name="exc_biceps_6_description">In standing position, back straight, barbell is held with wide-grip (hands apart on width slightly greater than the distance between shoulders):\n- take breath and then bend forearms trying not to move your chest by performing isometrical contraction of glutes, abdominal and paraspinal muscles;\n- exhale in final phase of movement.\nThis exercise involves mainly biceps and brachialis muscle.</string>

    <string name="exc_triceps_1_name">Exercise for triceps brachii muscle with use of lat pull down (hand of cable row is held with wide-grip)</string>
    <string name="exc_triceps_2_name">Exercise for triceps brachii muscle with use of lat pull down (hand of cable row is held with reverse grip)</string>
    <string name="exc_triceps_3_name">Alternate straightening forearms with use of lat pull down</string>
    <string name="exc_triceps_4_name">Straighten elbows with barbells in the lying position on bench</string>
    <string name="exc_triceps_5_name">Straighten elbows with dumbbells in lying position</string>
    <string name="exc_triceps_6_name">Flexing forearms to support back on benches</string>

    <string name="exc_triceps_1_description">In standing position, hands on lat pull down holder, elbows along trunk:\n- take breath and straight forearms trying not to tear elbows from trunk;\n- exhale in final phase of exercise.</string>
    <string name="exc_triceps_2_description">In standing position, facing the machine, arms at sides, bent at elbows, hands on the handles:\n- take breath and straighten forearms trying no to separate elbows from your body;\n- exhale in final phase of movement.\nReverse grip prevents training with heavy load that\'s why this exercise can only be done with small load in order to develop triceps brachii muscle and concentrate effort on head of this muscle.</string>
    <string name="exc_triceps_3_description">In standing position facing the machine, hand of lift is held with wide-grip:\n- take breath and straighten forearm;\n- exhale.\nThis exercise involves triceps brachii muscle, mainly its side head.</string>
    <string name="exc_triceps_4_description">In the lying position on bench, barbell is held with wide-grip, arms arranged vertically in relation to the bench:\n- take breath and bent arms trying not to dissuade too in back elbows while lowering the barbell at the height of forehead;\n- exhale in the final phase of movement.</string>
    <string name="exc_triceps_5_description">Lying on the ground, dumbbells is held in both hands, arms vertically to the ground:\n- take breath and bent arms controlling movement;\n- return to start position and exhale in final phase of movement.\nThis exercise is evenly involving all three heads of the triceps brachii muscle.</string>
    <string name="exc_triceps_6_description">Hands stacked at the end of the bench, feet based on the other bench, body suspended in the air:\n- take breath and bend your forearms and after that straighten them back (push back on them);\n- take breath in final phase of exercise.\nExercise engages triceps brachii muscle, pectorals and front part of shoulder muscles. On thighs you can put weight and thanks to it pushing will be harder and effort will be more intense.</string>

    <string name="exc_shoulders_1_name">Barbell press behind neck</string>
    <string name="exc_shoulders_2_name">Dumbbell floor press</string>
    <string name="exc_shoulders_3_name">Dumbbell side raise</string>
    <string name="exc_shoulders_4_name">Dumbbell front raise</string>
    <string name="exc_shoulders_5_name">Rising arms with dumbbells in lateral decubitus position</string>
    <string name="exc_shoulders_6_name">Alternately lifting arms to the side with using the low cable pulley</string>

    <string name="exc_shoulders_1_description">In sitting position, barbell is held with wide-grip behind neck:\n- take breath and push barbell vertically, without bending to much back;\n- exhale in final phase of movement.\nThis exercise involves deltoid muscle, mainly its middle part and rear as well as trapezius muscle, triceps brachii muscle and serratus anterior muscle.</string>
    <string name="exc_shoulders_2_description">In the sitting position on bench, dumbbell is held with wide-grip at shoulder level:\n- take breath and press dumbbell up to vertical straighten arms;\n- exhale in the final phase of movement.\nThis exercise involves deltoid, mainly its middle part as well as trapezius, serratur anterior muscle and tricpes branchii muscle.\nThis exercise can also be done in standing position or straightening arms alternately.</string>
    <string name="exc_shoulders_3_description">In standing position, lower limbs in slight stride, back straight, arms at side, dumbbells in hands:\n- rise arms to level(elbows slightly bent);\n- return to start position.\nThis exercise involves shoulder muscles, mainly middle part of them.\nThis exercise cannot be performed with high load. Series of 10&#8211;25 repetitions give best results.</string>
    <string name="exc_shoulders_4_description">In standing position, lower limbs in slight stride, dumbbells are held with wide-grip lying on thigh or slightly on side:\n- take breath and alternately rise arms forward at eye level;\n- exhale in final phase of movement.\nThis exercise involves mainly front part of shoulder muscles, part of the clavicular pectoralis major muscle and rest of deltoid muscle.</string>
    <string name="exc_shoulders_5_description">In lateral decubitus position on the floor or bench, dumbbells is held with wide-grip:\n- take breath and rise arm to level;\n- exhale in the final phase of movement.\nUnlike lifting arms in standing position which involves gradually deltoid muscle up to reaching maximum intensity of effort in the final phase (when arms come to level) in this exercise effort is focused in the initial phase of lifting. The best results are obtained by doing 10&#8211;20 repetitions.</string>
    <string name="exc_shoulders_6_description">Lift handle in your hand, arm along the trunk:\n- take breath and lift arm to horizon;\n- exhale in the final phase of movement.\nThis exercise develops deltoid, mainly the middle multipennate muscle ie. composed of several pen-shaped parts that\'s why it\'s so important to change angles under which rises arms in order to engage all muscle bands.</string>

    <string name="exc_chest_1_name">Incline bench press</string>
    <string name="exc_chest_2_name">Pumps (bending arms in front support)</string>
    <string name="exc_chest_3_name">Bending arms  on the armrests (swedish pumps)</string>
    <string name="exc_chest_4_name">Lifting dumbbells lying on your back</string>
    <string name="exc_chest_5_name">Dumbbell Flys</string>
    <string name="exc_chest_6_name">Pull-over with barbells in the suspine position on horizontal bench</string>

    <string name="exc_chest_1_description">In sitting position on the oblique bench (angle of the bench should be between 45 and 60 degrees), barbell is held with wide-grip on the level greater that distance between shoulders: -take breath and rise barbell in the level of indentation bridge: -press, exhale in the final phase of movement. This exercise involves pectoralis major muscle, mainly its collar part and front part of shoulder muscle, triceps brachii muscle and pectoralis minor muscle. It can be done using racks</string>
    <string name="exc_chest_2_description">Arms straighten based on ground, spaced shoulder width (or wider), feet near each other or slight gape between them: -take breath and bend arms so the chest will be near floor without bending over the back in the lumbar region; -exhale in the final phase of movement. This is an excellent exercise for the pectoralis major muscle and triceps brachii muscle. It can be done everywhere.</string>
    <string name="exc_chest_3_description">Arms straight, based on handrails, lower limbs hang without touching the floor: -take breath and bend completly forearms so that breast will be at the height of the ralling:- exhale at the final phase of exercise. The deeper trunk tilt forward the fuller commitment of pectorial muscles (the inner part of them) and vice versa the more straight torso the fuller triceps brachii muscles work.</string>
    <string name="exc_chest_4_description">In the lying position on horizontal bench, feet supported on the ground, upper limb bent at elbows, dumbells is held with wide-grip at the height of brest: -take breath and straighten upper limbs vertically and at the same turning the forearms so that hands will face each other: -when hands will be facing each other make isometric contraction in order to focus effort in sterno-ribbed part of pectoral major muscles: -exhale in final phase of movement. This exercise reminds lifting barbells but because of the greater amplitude of movement it promotes the pectorial major muscle tension.  When performing this exercise also works triceps and front part of the shoulder muscle.</string>
    <string name="exc_chest_5_description">Lying on a narrow bench which allows free movments of arms, dumbbel is held in the hands lifted upwards or slightly bent in elbows in order to relieve pressure on joints: -take breath and then spread out arm to the level; -back to vertical making exhale; -perform small isometric contraction in the final phase of movement in order to strengthen the work of sterno-ribbed part of te pectoral major muscle. This exercise must not be done with heavy loads. This exercise mainly focuses effot in the pectorial muscles bigger.This is the basic exercise which develops the chest muscles which also increases the capacity of lunges.</string>
    <string name="exc_chest_6_description">Arms lifted upward, barbell is held with wide-grip(grip the neck on witdh of shoulders): -take breath, taking to lungs as much air as possible and leave the barbell behind your head, slightly bending upper limbs in elbows; -exhale and return to start position. This exercise develops pectoralis major muscle lats as well as front toothed muscles, rhomboid muscles and pectoralis minor muscle.This exercise is made with a small load</string>

    <string name="exc_back_1_name">Wide grip pull up</string>
    <string name="exc_back_2_name">Chin up</string>
    <string name="exc_back_3_name">Pulling cable row to neck</string>
    <string name="exc_back_4_name">Rising dumbbells in kneel propped on the bench</string>
    <string name="exc_back_5_name">Vertical pulls barbell up to chin (narrow grip)</string>
    <string name="exc_back_6_name">Barbell shrug</string>

    <string name="exc_back_1_description">In the overhang on the stick, hands in the conversion, wide apart: -take breath and pull up so that chest will be near stick level: -exhale in final phase of movement -return to start position controlling movement during descend and then repeat whole exercise. This is perfect exercise but demanding quite large force. This exercise develops teres major muscle and doral muscles</string>
    <string name="exc_back_2_description">In the overhang on the stick, hands reversed, spaced on shoulder width: -take breath and throw out chest and pull up so thath chin will be on stick level: -exhale in final phase of movement. This exercise develops doral muscles and teres major muscle. For this reason it may be included in training arms plan. In exercise also takes part trapezius muscle, rhomboid muscle and chest muscles.</string>
    <string name="exc_back_3_description">In sitting position, face placed to machine, thighs is held by blocks, stick is held with wide-grip with widely spaced hands: -take breath and pull stick behind neck with elbows along the trunk: -exhale in final phase of movement. This is perfect exercise for increasing width of back muscles. It involves muscles lats (mainly their external fiber and lower).</string>
    <string name="exc_back_4_description">Dumbell is held in one hand with half conversion, second hand bend and bent at knee lower limb based on bench; -secure back, take breath and pull dumbell the most possible height, is helding arm near body and restoring hard elbow to the back: -exhale in the final phase of movement. In order to achieve maximum muscle tension you can slightly turn your chest in the final phase of the pull. This exercise involves mainly latissimus dorsi muscle, teres major muscle, the rear parts of the deltoid and trapezius and rhomboid muscles (in the final phase) and also flexor muscles of the arms (mainly biceps)</string>
    <string name="exc_back_5_description">In standing position, lower limbs in slight stride, back straight, barbell is held with wide-grip(hands apart from each other on the width of hands or slightly greater): -take breath, pull barbell along trunk to chin, rising elbows as high as possible: -while exhale control lowering the barbell so that it will be smooth.</string>
    <string name="exc_back_6_description">In standing position, facing the barbell, lower limbs in slight stride: -take barbell with hands with reverse grip -strongly straighten spine, stretch stomach muscles and perform arms rising. This exercise develops descending trapezius muscle.</string>

    <string name="exc_legs_1_name">Dumbbell squat</string>
    <string name="exc_legs_2_name">45 degree leg press</string>
    <string name="exc_legs_3_name">Straighten of lower limbs with the use of machine</string>
    <string name="exc_legs_4_name">Exercise for sciatic muscle-shin in standing position with use of machine</string>
    <string name="exc_legs_5_name">Standing one leg calf raise with dumbbell</string>
    <string name="exc_legs_6_name">Hack Calf Rise</string>

    <string name="exc_legs_1_description">In standing posiiton, lower limbs in slight stride, dumbbell are held in hands, arms fall down freely: -look straight ahead, take breath, slightly bend back and bend knees; when thighs will be at ground level, straight lower limbs and return to start position; -exhale. This exercise involves mainly quadriceps muscles of thigh and buttock muscles.</string>
    <string name="exc_legs_2_description">In the arrangement on the machine, spine adjacent to back of machine, feet apart not to wide: -take brearh, unlock the machine\'s protection and as hard as possible bend knees so that lower limbs will be near chest: -return to start position with exhale in the final phase of movement. If feet are arranged in lower part of platform, the quadriceps muscles are working primarily. If feet are wide apart, effort is directed to the adductor muscle</string>
    <string name="exc_legs_3_description">In sittingh position on the machine, hands clenched on poles or seats in order to keep torso still, lower limbs bent at knees and ankles stacked in rollers: -take breath and straighten limbs to set them to the level: -exhale in the final phase of movement. This is perfect isolated exercise for quadriceps. It must be said that the more leans back the greater will be back lean of plevis.</string>
    <string name="exc_legs_4_description">In standing position, chest based on stand, knees blocked, lower limbs straight: -take breath and bend knee: -exhale in final phase of movement. This exercise involves all sciatic muscle-shin and to a lesser extent, bulging calf muscles.</string>
    <string name="exc_legs_5_description">In standing position, toes resting on stand, dumbbell in one hand, other hand based on bracket for better balance: -climb on toes (plantar flexion), keeping knee in straight or slight flexion: -return to start position. This exercise involves triceps calf. In every repetition should be performed full bend to stretch the triceps calf</string>
    <string name="exc_legs_6_description">In sitting position, lower part of the thigh under block, toes on the stand, heel slightly lowered: -climb on toes (plantar bend). This exercise mainly involves the soleus.</string>

    <string name="exc_abs_1_name">Trunk slopes in lying position (crunch)</string>
    <string name="exc_abs_2_name">Raising the body from ground</string>
    <string name="exc_abs_3_name">Slopes trunk front with use of lat pull down</string>
    <string name="exc_abs_4_name">Rising the lower limbs on the inclide bench with flexion of the spine and lifting the plevis</string>
    <string name="exc_abs_5_name">Raising knees on the abdominal muscles machine</string>
    <string name="exc_abs_6_name">Raising lower limbs in overhang on the stick</string>

    <string name="exc_abs_1_description">Lying on the ground, hands behind head, thighs positioned vertically, knees bent: -take breath and rise your arms from ground, attract knees to head and bent the spine: -echale in the final phase of exercise. This exercise involves mainly the rectus abdominis. For more intensive work of oblique abdominal muscles just bent spine and attract alternately right elbow to left knee and left elbow to right knee</string>
    <string name="exc_abs_2_description">Lying on ground, lower limbs bent, feet on the floor, hands behind head: -take breath and raise body, arching your spine, make exhale in the final phase of exercise: -return to start position but in this time without lying completly on floor: -again raise body (in the stomach area should appear burning). This exercise involves muscles of the hip flexors.</string>
    <string name="exc_abs_3_description">In kneeling position, stick behind neck: -take breath and bend spine approaching bridge to pubic bone; -exhale in final phase of movement. This exercise cannot be done with heavy load. It\'s important to focus on work of muscles.</string>
    <string name="exc_abs_4_description">Lying on the inclide bench, hands on the railing or stick: -rise lower limbs to the vertical, then rise plevis, bend the spine and try to touch your head with knees. Exercise engages iliopsoas muscle while rising lower limbs, tensor fasciae latae and biceps of thigh (part of quadriceps muscle) during the bending of the spine is engaging abdominal pressure.</string>
    <string name="exc_abs_5_description">Based on elbows, back locked: -take breath and pull knees to your chest, bend back to arc in order to streetch muscles abdominal pressure: -exhale in final phase of movement. This exercise involves muscles of hip flexors, mainly ilio-lumbar muscles as well as the obliques and the rectus abdominis, the latter is engaged intensively in its lower part.</string>
    <string name="exc_abs_6_description">In the overhang on the stick: -take breath and raise knees as high as possible trying to get closer pubic bone to bridge by bend of the spine: -exhale in the final phase of exercise. This exercise affects ilio-lumbar muscles, rectus femoris muscle and tensor fascia lata (while rising lower limbs).</string>

    <string name="difficulty_1_name">Very Easy</string>
    <string name="difficulty_2_name">Easy</string>
    <string name="difficulty_3_name">Medium</string>
    <string name="difficulty_4_name">Hard</string>
    <string name="difficulty_5_name">Very Hard</string>

    <!-- About Fragment-->
    <string name="about_description">Great, smart and versatile training application made for the best and the strongest people walking on Earth</string>
    <string name="about_follow">Follow us on GitHub</string>
    <string name="about_copyright">© RafPep Inc. 2016 All rights reserved</string>

    <!-- Settings Fragment -->
    <string name="settings_language_title">Language</string>
    <string name="settings_language_subtitle">Current language:</string>
    <string name="settings_theme_title">Theme</string>
    <string name="settings_theme_subtitle">Current theme:</string>
    <string name="settings_default_tab_title">Default tab</string>
    <string name="settings_default_tab_subtitle">Current default tab:</string>
    <string name="settings_stats_title">Clear statistics</string>
    <string name="settings_stats_subtitle">Clears all your local statistics</string>
    <string name="settings_server_title">Server address</string>
    <string name="settings_server_subtitle">Current server address:</string>

    <string name="settings_language_polish">Polish</string>
    <string name="settings_language_english">English</string>

    <string name="settings_server_label">Insert new server address</string>
    <string name="settings_server_save_button">Save</string>
    <string name="settings_server_restore_button">Restore default</string>

    <!-- Theme color names -->
    <string name="theme_color_red">Red</string>
    <string name="theme_color_pink">Pink</string>
    <string name="theme_color_purple">Purple</string>
    <string name="theme_color_deep_purple">Deep Purple</string>
    <string name="theme_color_indigo">Indigo</string>
    <string name="theme_color_blue">Blue</string>
    <string name="theme_color_light_blue">Light Blue</string>
    <string name="theme_color_cyan">Cyan</string>
    <string name="theme_color_teal">Teal</string>
    <string name="theme_color_green">Green</string>
    <string name="theme_color_light_green">Light Green</string>
    <string name="theme_color_lime">Lime</string>
    <string name="theme_color_yellow">Yellow</string>
    <string name="theme_color_amber">Amber</string>
    <string name="theme_color_orange">Orange</string>
    <string name="theme_color_deep_orange">Deep Orange</string>
    <string name="theme_color_brown">Brown</string>

    <string name="theme_name">Theme Name</string>

    <string name="alert_title">Warning</string>
    <string name="alert_msg_training_running">Your training activity is still running. If you want to change the tab, end the training first.</string>
    <string name="alert_msg_cardio_running">Your cardio activity is still running. If you want to change the tab, end the running first.</string>
    <string name="alert_positive_button">OK</string>

    <!-- Toast messages -->
    <string name="toast_msg_login_error">Authentication error</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_theme_changed">App theme has been changed</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_language_changed">App language has been changed</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_default_tab_changed">Default app tab has been changed</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_stats_cleared">Local statistics has been cleared</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_network_error">Network not available</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_server_address_error">Server address is incorrect</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_server_address_changed">Server address has been changed</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_server_address_restored">Default server address has been restored</string>
</resources>